Oats and beans and barley grow
Do you or I or anyone know
How oats and beans and barley grow
Plant your seeds down nice and low
Pat the ground and watch them grow
Wiggle your fingers let rain fall
Now reach up and grow so tall
Sway to the left sway to the right
Stretch your leaves into the light
Find your grown up face to face
Copy the moves right in your place
Oats and beans and barley grow
Do you or I or anyone know
How oats and beans and barley grow
Can you stamp stamp stamp stamp
Can you clap clap clap clap
Turn around and bend your knees
Stand up tall and everybody freeze
Oats and beans and barley grow
Do you or I or anyone know
How oats and beans and barley grow
Little seed and great big tree
Thanks for dancing here with me